A Guide to the Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JHPI) records FA476
Rockefeller Archive Center
Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JHPI) records
1940-2002
Rockefeller Archive Center
Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated.
FA476
145.2 Cubic Feet
Records consist of approximately 120 standard record storage boxes.
Accruals note
A portion of Accession 2006:097 -- Boxes 118 and 120 containing Board Minutes, Bylaws, and Certificate of Incorporation --- were officially deaccessioned in January 2007. Portions of Box 118 remain in the collection.
Scope and Contents note
The collection primarily consists of grant files, general files, administrative records and financial records.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. deposited the records at the Rockefeller Archive Center in April 1985.
RAC received Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. records as early as 1977. Official accession documentation is available beginning in 1990 (Accession 1990:115). Additions and accruals to the collection have been received in multiple accessions, and continue periodically as applicable.
Conditions Governing Access note
Records more than 15 years old are open for scholarly research, with prior archival review.
In accordance with standard Rockefeller Archive Center practices, all personnel and associated employee files, and select financial materials are restricted from scholarly access.
Material which provides the names, correspondence or activities of living members of the Rockefeller family, and/or documents the net worth of Rockefeller family members, is restricted from scholarly access.
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Reference and/or RAC Head of Archival Services.
Related Archival Materials note
American Conservation Association records. Kenneth Chorley papers. Harold P. Fabian papers. Laurance S. Rockefeller papers.
Biographical/Historical note
The original purposes of the Jackson Hole Preserve were to restore, protect,and preserve primitive grandeur and natural beauty for the benefit of the public; to provide for the protection, feeding, and propagation of wild game; and to maintain the historic and scientific features of picturesque areas.
Since 1940, when the preserve was founded by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and his son Laurance, JHPI has given to the United States more than 33,000 acres of land for national parks in the Grand Tetons of Wyoming, the Virgin Islands in the Caribbean, and New York State. In addition, the preserve has built visitor facilities in these areas and contributed several million dollars to their maintenance.
In 1958, Jackson Hole Preserve established a new organization, the American Conservation Association, to carry on the educational, research, and citizen action activities that the Preserve felt were beyond its own capabilities.
Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated.
- General Files and Grants, 1
  - Concessions (CBPI & GTLC) (Box 8)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Restricted from scholarly access - financial material.
  - Annual Report- State of Wyoming (Box 8)
    Open for scholarly access, with prior archival review. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours. Records which document the activities of living members of the Rockefeller family are restricted.
  - Agent in Virgin Islands (Richard E. Grunert) (Box 8)
  - Agent (Wyoming) Carl L. Lathrop (Box 8)
  - Virgin Islands Government Annual Report, 1976-1986 (Box 8)
  - Virgin Islands Government Annual Report, 1956-1976 (Box 8)
  - Annual Report and Franchise Tax - Virgin Islands (Box 8)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. Financial Statements (Box 8)
  - CBI/GTLC Agendas & Board Meetings (Box 8)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company (GTLC) - Agendas and Board of Directors Meetings, 1983 September 12 (Box 8)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company (GTLC) - Agendas and Board of Directors Meetings, 1981, 1982 (Box 8)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company (GTLC) - Agendas and Board of Directors Meetings, 1979, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company (GTLC) - Agendas and Board of Directors Meetings, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company (GTLC) - Agendas and Board of Directors Meetings, 1977 (Box 8)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company (GTLC) - Agendas and Board of Directors Meetings, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company (GTLC) - Agendas and Board of Directors Meetings, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company (GTLC) - Agendas and Board of Directors Meetings, 1974 (Box 8)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company (GTLC) - Agendas and Board of Directors Meetings, 1973 (Box 8)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund Inc. Expenditure Responsibility (Box 10)
  - Bank Resolutions (Box 10)
  - Statement on Jackson Hole Airport - Drafts 1&2 (Box 10)
  - JHPI Project - Re: Creation of Grand Teton Nation Park - Book by Prof. Rover W. Righter, 1980 (Box 10)
  - The Early Days of Jackson Hole by Virginia Huidekoper (Box 10)
  - Ornithological Study of the State Parks and Historic Sites of New York Project (Box 10)
  - Natural Heritage Trust (Box 10)
  - Biography of David E. Jackson Project, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Landscape Development Plan Supplement - Jackson Hole Golf and Tennis Club, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Spring Creek Ranch, WY (Box 10)
  - The Lucas Place (Box 10)
  - Finance Committee Meeting, 1982 December (Box 10)
  - ACA-JHPI - Board Meetings, 1966-1972 (Box 10)
  - ACA-JHPI - Board Meetings, 1973-1975 (Box 10)
  - ACA-JHPI - Board Meetings, 1976 (Box 10)
  - ACA-JHPI - Board Meetings, 1977 (Box 10)
  - JHPI, 1978 (Box 10)
  - JHPI - Agenda - Board Meetings, 1979 (Box 10)
  - JHPI - Agenda - Board Meetings, 1980 (Box 10)
  - JHPI - Agenda - Board Meetings, 1981 (Box 10)
  - JHPI - Agenda - Board Meetings, 1982 (Box 10)
  - JHPI - Agenda, 1983 (Box 10)
  - JHPI, 1967 (Box 10)
  - JHPI, 1968 (Box 10)
  - Pollution: the Waters of the Earth (Box 12)
  - Birds in the Balance (Box 12)
  - Fish & Man - Conflict in the Atlantic Estuaries, 2 copies. (Box 12)
  - Behold the Turtle (Box 12)
  - Outlines of Environmental Education (Box 12)
  - The Edge of the Sea (Box 12)
  - Under the Sea Wind (Box 12)
  - A Naturalist in Alaska (Box 12)
  - The Pacific Islands Revised Edition (Box 12)
  - Animal Behavior (Box 12)
  - The Exploration of the Colorado River (Box 12)
  - Puffins (Box 12)
  - Quotable Quotes: Relation to Conservation in General and National Parks in Particular (Box 12)
  - Extinct and Vanishing Birds of the World (Box 12)
  - Classroom Out-of-Doors- Education through School Camping (Box 12)
  - National Geographic Map of Vacation lands of the United States and Southern Canada (Box 12)
  - National Geographic Reprint - World's Tallest Tree Discovered (Box 12)
  - National Geographic, 1964 June (Box 12)
  - National Geographic, 1964 February (Box 12)
  - National Geographic, 1964 January (Box 12)
  - National Geographic Reprint - Our National Parks (Box 12)
  - Audio Reel - Editorial Meeting, 1958 June 6 (Box 12)
    RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
  - Audio Reel - Arlene Francis (Hildegrade) (Box 12)
  - Conservation Quotes (Box 12)
  - Pollution: the Land we live on (Box 12)
  - Pollution: the Air we breathe (Box 12)
  - The Sea Around Us (Box 12)
  - JY Ranch- Corporate Matters, 1946 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch- Equipment, Supplies, etc., 1946-1949 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - General, 1945-1947 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - General, 1959 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - General, 1958 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - General, 1957 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - General, 1955-1957 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Mathews Red & Belle, 1959-1960 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Mathews Red & Belle, 1958 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Mathews Red & Belle, 1956-1957 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Mathews Red & Belle/ Gift JDR Jr., 1955-1961 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Mathews Red, 1954-1955 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Mathews Red, 1953 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Mathews Red, 1952 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Mathews Red, 1949-1951 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Equipment and Furnishings, 1953-1955 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Equipment and Furnishings, 1950-1952 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Equipment, Supplies, Etc./ Hydro-Electric Plant, 1946-1948 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Accounting, 1959 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Accounting General, 1958 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Accounting, 1957 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Accounting, 1956 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Accounting General, 1955 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Finance Budget, 1954 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Finance Budget, 1953 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Finance Budget, 1952 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Finance Budget, 1951 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Finance Budget, 1950 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Finance Budget, 1949 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Finance Budget, 1948 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Finance Budget, 1947 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Finance Budget, 1946 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Finance Budget, 1948-1949 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Footbridge & Dam, 1946 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Horses, 1951-1952 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Insurance, 1952 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Lodge, 1950-1951 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Recreation Hall, 1947 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Roads, 1950-1953 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - JDR, Jr. & KC, 1953-1954 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Visits (by name), 1953 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Visits (by name), 1952 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Visits (by name), 1951 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Visits (by name), 1955 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - JDR, Jr. & K.C., 1951-1952 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - JDR, Jr. & K.C., 1949-1950 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Crown Prince of Japan, 1953 (Box 28)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1945-1947 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Wallaces, 1947-1948 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits, 1946-1948 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Rockefeller, JDR Jr., 1947-1949 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Rockefeller, David, 1946-1949 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - JDR 3rd, 1949 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1945-1949 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Chorley, Kenneth, 1962-1963 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Chorley, Kenneth, 1960 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - JDR, Jr. & KC - General Correspondence, 1958 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - JDR, Jr. & KC - General Correspondence, 1957 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - JDR, Jr. & KC - General Correspondence, 1956 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - JDR, Jr. & KC - General Correspondence, 1955 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits, 1958-1962 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Individuals (A-Z), 1963 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Individuals (A-Z), 1962 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Individuals (A-Z), 1961 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Individuals (A-Z), 1960 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Individuals (A-Z), 1959 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Individuals (A-Z), 1958 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Individuals (A-Z), 1957 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Individuals (A-Z), 1956 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Visits - Individuals (A-Z), 1954-1955 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Property Taxes, 1951 (Box 29)
  - JHPI- JY Ranch- RE-29 JHP Property Held- 1941 P-151 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch- Construction- New Cabin (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Construction, 1960 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Construction, 1958-1959 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Construction, 1957 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - JH3-2 Personal Property Taxes, 1951 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Property Acquisition, 1949-1954 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - JHP3-C Form 990-A, 1951-1953 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - JHP 3D- Internal Revenue Form 990 and Correspondence, 1941-1953 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Report on Private Land Situation/Grand Teton National Park, 1951 October 15 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Property Acquisition - General RE 32 Information P-153, 1949-1954 (Box 29)
  - JY Ranch - Property Acquisition - General RE 32 Information P-153, 1930-1945 (Box 29)
  - Property Holdings - Site Maps, 1928-1931 (Box 30)
  - Aerial Photography, 1943-1946 (Box 30)
  - Albright, Horace M., 1946-1948 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "A", 1946-1948 (Box 30)
  - Bar BC, 1948-1950 (Box 30)
  - Barnett, Bill, 1947-1948 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "BA", 1945-1949 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Bear Claw, 1949 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Bear Claw, 1945-1948 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "BE" Cross Reference, 1946-1947 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Boyer, Allston, 1946-1947 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - BI-BL, 1944-1947 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Brant Irving, 1945-1946 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Brookings Institution, 1945 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "BR", 1945-1947 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "BU-BY", 1945-1949 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Chorley, Kenneth, 1946-1949 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "CA", 1946-1949 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Contributions (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "CH-CO", 1941-1949 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "CR-CY", 1946-1948 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Darling, Jay N., 1945 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "DAE-DE", 1944-1948 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Drury, Newton B., 1945-1949 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Dude Ranchers Association, 1947-1949 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "DJ-DU", 1945-1949 (Box 30)
  - General Correspondence - Elk Ranch, 1946-1949 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Eastside Highway, 1947-1948 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence Economic - Study of Jackson Hole, 1946-1947 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "Elk Herd", 1945-1949 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "E", 1945-1948 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence- Jackson Hole Preserve Inc. Finance, 1945-1948 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Fabian, Harold, 1949 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Fabian, Harold P., 1947-1948 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Fabian, Harold P., 1945-1964 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Financial Report, 1947 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Financial Report Audit, 1947 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Financial Report, 1946 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Fish and Wildlife Service, 1947-1949 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "FA-FJ", 1946-1949 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Frank, Paul B., 1945 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "FO-FR", 1945-1947 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "GA-GJ", 1945-1947 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "GO", 1945-1947 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Grand Teton National Park, 1942-1944 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "GR-GU", 1945-1948 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "HA", 1946-1947 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "HE", 1946 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Highways and Roads, 1942-1948 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "HJ", 1946-1947 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "HO-HY", 1945-1949 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Ickes, Harold L., 1945 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Insurance, 1945-1948 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - Irrigation, 1944-1946 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - "J", 1946-1949 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - JHPI Annual Report, 1946 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - JHPI Finance Budget, 1945-1948 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - JHPI Finance Budgets, 1944-1948 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence - JHPI - Report A.E. Kendrew, 1942 (Box 30)
  - JHPI, 1946-1949 (Box 30)
  - 1930-1933 Conference (Box 30)
  - Finance, 1949 (Box 31)
  - Correspondence - JHPI Finance - Transfer of Stocks, 1945-1947 (Box 31)
  - JHPI Finance - Special Account, 1946-1949 (Box 31)
  - Jackson Hole Monument - General, 1945-1949 (Box 31)
  - Jackson Hole National Monument Meeting, 1944 July 31-August 2 (Box 31)
  - Jackson Hole National Monument - Transfer of Lands, 1949 (Box 31)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park, 1945-1947 (Box 31)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park Corporate Matters, 1945-1947 (Box 31)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park Equipment, 1946-1947 (Box 31)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park, 1948-1949 (Box 31)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park - Finance, 1949 (Box 31)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park - Finance, 1947 (Box 31)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park - Finance Budget, 1946-1949 (Box 31)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park - Meetings, 1946-1949 (Box 31)
  - Jackson Lake Lodge, 1946-1949 (Box 31)
  - Jackson Lake Tourist Center, 1945-1946 (Box 31)
  - Jenny Luke Ranch, 1946-1949 (Box 31)
  - JY Ranch- 1948-1949 (Box 31)
  - Correspondence - "J", 1947-1949 (Box 31)
  - Correspondence - Kendrew, A.E., 1946 (Box 31)
  - Correspondence - Kimmel, J.D., 1946-1949 (Box 31)
  - Correspondence - "K", 1946-1950 (Box 31)
  - Krug, J.A., 1946-1949 (Box 31)
  - Correspondence - "KL-KZ", 1946-1949 (Box 31)
  - Correspondence - "L", 1946-1949 (Box 31)
  - Lodges, 1945-1946 (Box 31)
  - Mathews, Red, 1946-1949 (Box 31)
  - Correspondence - "MA", 1946-1949 (Box 31)
  - Master Plan Development Outline - Grand Teton National Park, 1947-1949 (Box 31)
  - Master Plan Development Outline - Grand Teton National Park, 1944-1946 (Box 31)
  - Correspondence - "MC", 1946-1947 (Box 31)
  - Menor's Ferry, 1946-1949 (Box 31)
  - Miller, Leslie A., 1945-1949 (Box 31)
  - ME, MI (Box 31)
  - Moran Tree Planting, 1947-1949 (Box 31)
  - MO, 1945-1949 (Box 31)
  - Murie, Olavs J., 1945-1949 (Box 31)
  - Museum, 1944 (Box 31)
  - "Mu-My", 1947-1948 (Box 31)
  - National Parks, 1945-1949 (Box 31)
  - Correspondence - "N"- 1946-1948 (Box 31)
  - O'Mahoney, Rider, 1945-1948 (Box 31)
  - Oil and Gas Leases (Box 31)
  - Osborn H. Fairfield Jr. (Box 31)
  - O (Box 31)
  - "PA-PH" (Box 31)
  - Miscellaneous Maps and Blueprints (Box 31)
  - Property (Box 32)
  - Property - Purchase (Box 32)
  - Property- Leases (Box 32)
  - Vol. II - (Papers) Part 3 - Jackson Hole National Monument - Compendium (Box 32)
  - Vol. II - (Papers) Part 2 - Jackson Hole National Monument - Compendium (Box 32)
  - Jackson Hole National Monument- Compendium - Vol. I - Chronology - Index (Box 32)
  - Vol. IV - Maps - Jackson Hole National Monument- Compendium (Box 32)
  - Vol. II - (Papers) Part 1 - Jackson Hole National Monument - Compendium (Box 32)
  - Report on Jackson Hole Project to Laurance S. Rockefeller from Harold P. Fabian (Box 32)
  - Property - Privately Owned (Box 32)
  - Property- Purchase - Abercrombie (Box 32)
  - Property - Purchase - Barker (Box 32)
  - Property - Purchase - Chambers (Box 32)
  - Property - Purchase - Feuz (Box 32)
  - Property - Purchase - Huff (Box 32)
  - Property - Purchase - Johnson, Effie J. (Box 32)
  - Property - Purchase - R Lazy S. (Box 32)
  - Property - Purchase - Lucas (Box 32)
  - Property - Purchase - Wilson (Box 32)
  - Property - Transfer (Rockefeller) (Box 32)
  - Property - Acreage (Box 32)
  - Property - Sale (Box 32)
  - Property - Sale - Kimmel (Box 32)
  - Proposed National Monument - Sen. O'Mahoney, 1943-1945 (Box 32)
  - Public Lands - Withdrawal (Box 32)
  - Public Relations Study (Box 32)
  - Publicity (Box 32)
  - Publicity - Magazine (Box 32)
  - Publicity- Magazine - "Heard About Jackson Hole?" Publicity- N agazine- "Heard About Jackson Hole?" (Box 32)
  - Publicity - Newspaper (Box 32)
  - "Pi- Py" (Box 32)
  - Publicity - Pamphlets - "Facts About Jackson Hole" (Box 32)
  - Resor Stanley (Box 32)
  - "Ra-Rh" (Box 32)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. (Box 32)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr.- Duplicate Copies (Box 32)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. (Box 32)
  - "T" (Box 32)
  - Transportation (Box 32)
  - Roads (Box 32)
  - "Ri- Ry" (Box 32)
  - "Sa-Sc" (Box 32)
  - "Se-Sh" (Box 32)
  - "Si-Sk" (Box 32)
  - "Sl-Sq" (Box 32)
  - Snake River (Box 32)
  - "St-Sy" (Box 32)
  - U.S. (Gov't)- Interior Dept. National Park Service (Box 32)
  - Visits - Jackson Hole (Box 32)
  - Visits- Jackson Hole - Kenneth Chorley (Box 32)
  - Visits - Jackson Hole (Alphabetically) (Box 32)
  - "U-V" (Box 32)
  - U.S. (Gov't) Senate - Bills, Resolutions (Box 32)
  - Water Rights (Box 32)
  - Webb, Vanderbilt (Box 32)
  - Wentworth, Jack (Box 32)
  - "Wa-We" (Box 32)
  - Winger, Richard (Box 32)
  - "Wh-Wi" (Box 32)
  - Woods, Len (Box 32)
  - Wyoming (State) vs. Franke, Paul R. (Box 32)
  - Wyoming (State) - Legislation - JT Resolution - Luman & Buchemoth (Box 32)
  - "Wo-Wy" (Box 32)
  - "X-Z" (Box 32)
  - JHPI (Box 33)
  - Bear Paw Ranch, 1950 (Box 33)
  - Bear Paw Trails, 1952 (Box 33)
  - Best, William, 1955 (Box 33)
  - Burt, S., 1951 (Box 33)
  - Camp Cady Project (Box 33)
  - Chorley, Kenneth, 1950-1952, 1953-1954 (Box 33)
  - Conservation Foundation Reports, 1950 (Box 33)
  - Concessions Study (Box 33)
  - Concessions- 1953 (Box 33)
  - Contributions - Utah State Park Recreation Commission and Sugarhouse Park Authority - General Correspondence (Box 33)
  - Contributions - Utah State Park Recreation Commission and Sugarhouse Park Authority - Reports and Photos (Box 33)
  - Cunningham Cabin, 1952 (Box 33)
  - Crandall Moran Studio, 1955 (Box 33)
  - Dam, 1950 (Box 33)
  - Dinosaur National Monument, 1950 (Box 33)
  - Drury, N., 1950-1951 (Box 33)
  - Elk Herd, 1950 (Box 33)
  - Elk Ranch, 1950 (Box 33)
  - Fabian, Harold P., 1957-1958 (Box 33)
  - Fabian, Harold P., 1956 (Box 33)
  - Fabian, Harold P., 1955 (Box 33)
  - Fabian, Harold P., 1953 (Box 33)
  - Fabian, Harold P., 1950-1952 (Box 33)
  - Fesslers Store, 1950 (Box 33)
  - Files, 1950 (Box 33)
  - Glauser, Gertrude, 1954-1955 (Box 33)
  - Grand Teton National Park, 1950-1952 (Box 33)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Monthly Reports, 1950-1952 (Box 33)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Monthly Reports, 1953 (Box 33)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Property Purchase, 1950-1951 (Box 33)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Property Purchase, 1954 (Box 33)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Property Purchase, 1953 (Box 33)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Property Purchase, 1952 (Box 33)
  - High Soco Tract (Box 33)
  - High Soco Tract- Pamphlets, Booklets, etc. (Box 33)
  - Izaak Walton League of America, 1950 (Box 33)
  - Finance - Special Account - Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 33)
  - P.R. Applicants, 1954-1955 (Box 33)
  - Finance - Budget, 1950-1952 (Box 33)
  - Finance - Audit, Lincoln G. Kelly, 1949-1950 (Box 33)
  - JHPI, 1952 (Box 33)
  - Finance, 1950-1952 (Box 33)
  - Meetings, 1950-1951 (Box 33)
  - Finance - Account - Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 33)
  - Jackson Hole Visits (by name), 1950-1951 (Box 33)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Jackson Hole Visits (Individuals A-Z), 1955 (Box 33)
  - Jackson Hole - Visits (by name), 1952-1954 (Box 33)
  - Jackson Hole - Rodeo and Racing Association, 1950 (Box 33)
  - Jackson Hole National Monument - Transfer of Land, 1950 (Box 33)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park, 1950-1951 (Box 34)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park, 1952 (Box 34)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park, 1953 (Box 34)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park - Finance - Audit, 1950 (Box 34)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park - Finance, 1950-1951 (Box 34)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park - Finance - Audit, 1951 (Box 34)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park - Finance, 1952 (Box 34)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park - Finance, 1953 (Box 34)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park - Meetings, 1950-1951 (Box 34)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park - Meetings, 1952-1955 (Box 34)
  - Jackson Lake Lodge - Clippings, 1955 (Box 34)
  - Report on Jackson Hole Project to Laurance S. Rockefeller from Harold P. Fabian (Box 34)
  - JY Ranch, 1950-1954 (Box 34)
  - Meetings, General, 1957 (Box 34)
  - Meetings, Transportation, 1958 (Box 34)
  - Meetings, Transportation, 1957 (Box 34)
  - Meetings, General, 1958 (Box 34)
  - Meetings, General, 1959 (Box 34)
  - Meetings, General, 1960 (Box 34)
  - Meetings, General, 1961 (Box 34)
  - Meetings, Annual Meeting, 1961 July 14 (Box 34)
  - Meetings, 1954 (Box 34)
  - Meetings, 1953 (Box 34)
  - Meetings, 1952 (Box 34)
  - Minute Book, 1940 (Box 34)
  - Meetings, General, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Meetings, General, 1955 (Box 34)
  - Moran (Box 34)
  - Museum, 1953-1956 (Box 34)
  - Maps - Grand Teton National Park, 1950 (Box 34)
  - Maps - Correspondence (by name), 1950 (Box 34)
  - Maude Noble Cabin, 1950 (Box 34)
  - Menor's Ferry, 1950 (Box 34)